<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Emmanuella Rumanti</title><link>https://amuritna.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Emmanuella Rumanti</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© 2024 Emmanuella Rumanti</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://amuritna.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Presenting MATLAB Figures in a Programmatically Generated HTML Document</title><link>https://amuritna.github.io/posts/matlab-html/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://amuritna.github.io/posts/matlab-html/</guid><description>&lt;hr>
&lt;p>As my projects progressed, the number of MATLAB figures to deal with at a time began to go past twenty, and I started developed frustration with MATLAB&amp;rsquo;s default way of arranging and displaying figures.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Here are some of them:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Each chart is limited by the size of the figure window, and each figure window is limited by the size of the device screen.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Therefore, to be able to display more figures, more windows have to launched. I started to feel messy once I started dealing with dozens of figures at a time.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Individual figures cannot be wider or longer than device screen width or height, respectively.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Having to manually close or drag around the figure windows every time I re-run the script.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Most importantly: You can show charts side-by-side in the same window — using subplot or the newer tiledlayout — but control over layout is limited.
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>For instance, tile spacing only has four options: &lt;code>loose&lt;/code>, &lt;code>compact&lt;/code>, &lt;code>tight&lt;/code>, &lt;code>none&lt;/code> (and &lt;code>none&lt;/code> does not really &lt;em>feel&lt;/em> like &amp;ldquo;no margins&amp;rdquo;, for me).&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Since I felt that it was beginning to affect my work in a less ideal way, I began to wonder about the alternatives. What came to mind afterwards was programmatically exporting all the figures created and accessing them using a different application — but we can still go further.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://amuritna.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://amuritna.github.io/about/</guid><description>&lt;p>Hello! My name is Emmanuella Rumanti, also known as amuritna &lt;a href="https://amuritna.github.io/about/#notes">[1]&lt;/a>. I can be contacted &lt;a href="mailto:amuritna@gmail.com">via e-mail&lt;/a>. You can also find me on &lt;a href="https://linkedin.com/in/emmanuella-rumanti/">LinkedIn&lt;/a> and &lt;a href="https://github.com/amuritna/">GitHub&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>At the moment, I am affliated with the School of Electrical Engineering and Informatics at &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bandung_Institute_of_Technology">Institut Teknologi Bandung&lt;/a>, Indonesia, where I am in my last year of pursuing a B.S. in Electrical Engineering. My current work — my team&amp;rsquo;s capstone design project — focuses on the design of specialized hardware to secure voice communication on an untrusted device.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>[Repost] Modular Origami</title><link>https://amuritna.github.io/posts/modular-origami/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 14:14:53 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://amuritna.github.io/posts/modular-origami/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;em>Note: This is a post originally published on December 22, 2019 on my old site. It has been reposted here for archival purposes.&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>If a &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Modular_origami">modular origami&lt;/a> construction is a book of fiction, then it is an anthology of tales, not a novel.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>